Hi, welcome to session 17,
嗨，欢迎来到第 17 节课，
in this session, we're going to learn about
在这次课程中，我们将学习，
playing in any key, any place on the neck,
如何在任何调，在琴颈上任何地方弹奏，
learning the entire fretboard,
学习整个指板，
and we're going to learn the wonder of three note on a string scales,
我们将学习弦乐音阶上三个音符的神奇之处，
what they are
它们是什么，
and how many great sounds you can pull out of these scales,
以及可以从这些音阶中出现多少很棒的声音，
we're also going to learn about triplets, a new rhythmic concept,
我们还将学习三连音，一种新的节奏概念，
and we're going to talk about hammer-ons and pull-offs
我们将讨论击弦和勾弦，
as they relate to three note on a string scales,
因为它们与弦乐音阶上的三个音符有关，
in the how music works section,
在音乐的工作原理部分，
we're going to cover what seventh chords are,
我们将讨论什么是第七和弦，
how to build them and how to use them.
如何建建它们以及如何使用它们。
So, let's go ahead and get started.
所以让我们继续并开始。
Okay, there's such a wonderful advantage to learning the entire neck of the instrument,
好的，学习乐器的整个琴颈有一个非常好的优势，
most guitar players learn the first position
大多数吉他演奏者学会了第一把位，
and they never even bother to get up into the upper [registers] of the instrument
他们甚至从来没有费心去进入乐器的上面音域，
and they just don't know what what notes these are,
他们不知道这些是什么音符，
what note is this, What note is that,
这是什么音符，那是什么音符，
they just kind of get lost as you get going up.
随着（指板）上升，他们就会迷失。
Now, we've talked about what the notes are on the sixth string and the fifth string,
我们已经讨论了第六弦和第五弦上的音符，
okay, there was one simple exercise that has helped me learn the entire neck of the guitar,
好的，有一个简单的练习帮助我学会了吉他的整个琴颈，
it's real easy for me to explain
这对我来说很容易解释，
and it took me probably three months
我可能花了三个月时间，
to actually get it in my tool belt of things
把它放进我的工具带中，
I can do as a guitar player,
我可以作为吉他演奏者使用，
and I tell you I use it every time I try and play a solo,
我告诉你，我每次试着 solo 的时候都会用到它，
and every time I'm in a studio session or any type of solo situation,
每当我在录音室或任何类型的 solo 情况下，
I use a simple concept, called three note on a string scales.
我都会使用一个简单的概念，称为弦上的三个音符。
The name is pretty self explanatory,
这个名字不言自明，
basically, here's the whole idea,
基本上，这就是整个想法，
you take a major scale,
你用一个大调音阶，
but I want you to play three notes on every string of that major scale,
但我要你弹奏三个音符在那个大调音阶的每根弦上，
so as you going up the major scale,
所以当你提升大调音阶时，
every three notes you're gonna be on a new string.
每三个音符在一根弦上，你将会有一条新的路线。
Okay, so you'll find that as we play this,
好的，你会发现，当我们演奏这个的时候，
it involves your hand to stretch quite a bit more
你的手要伸展的更多一点，
than we've normally stretched up until this point,
比起我们平时，
and it gets you working slowly up the neck of the guitar.
它会让你慢慢地在吉他的琴颈上工作。
Now, what has helped me as I'm doing this scale is
当我做这个音阶时，帮助我的是，
to say and play the notes,
说和弹奏音符，
what's the goal of this,
这样做的目的是什么，
not just to learn another pattern,
不仅是为了学习另一种模式，
but to be able to learn the neck of your guitar.
也是为了能够学习吉他的琴颈。
So let's, we're going to start it off,
所以让我们开始吧，
we're going to start off in the key of F,
我们从 F 调开始，
since that's the lowest one down here,
因为这是这里最低的，
what is the key of F having it, a Bb,
F 调有什么， Bb ，
remember that, F G A Bb C D E F is the F major scale
记得吗， F G A Bb C D E F 是 F 大调音阶，
and we're going to do it three notes per string.
我们每根弦要做三个音符。
So here we go,
我们开始吧，
we have F, then G, then A,
我们有 F G ，然后是 A ，
now I can go to the next string, Bb C D,
现在我可以转到下一根弦， Bb C D ，
notice how wide I have to have my hand in order to cover that,
注意我的手要有多宽才能覆盖它，
that's going to be real important how wide you can stretch your hand,
你可以把你的手伸展多宽是非常重要的，
next string, I go E F G,
下一根弦是 E F G ，
next string I have A Bb, don't forget the Bb C,
下一根弦是 A Bb C ，
then I shift up, I'm slowly shifting up positions,
然后我移动，我在慢慢地移动位置，
D E F,
D E F ，
G A Bb.
G A Bb 。
Okay, so in the course of that,
好的，在这个过程中，
I have shifted my hand three times,
我移动了我的手三次，
but I was able to grab another five or six notes
但我能够从中抓起另外五六个音符，
out of the major scale coming down here,
从这里的大调音阶中，
because I did three notes on a string.
因为我在一根弦上做了三个音符。
Let's do that one more time,
让我们再来一次，
starts on an F,
从 F 开始，
F G A Bb C D E F G A Bb C D E F G A Bb.
F G A Bb C D E F G A Bb C D E F G A Bb 。
Okay, let's do it one more time,
好的，我们再来一次，
this time I want you to say them with me,
这一次我希望你和我一起说，
as you're playing them,
当你在演奏它们的时候，
okay, remember to stretch out that hand,
好的，记得伸展那只手，
as far as your left hand and stretching goes,
随着你的左手伸展，
okay, we did a little stretching exercise at the very beginning,
好的，我们在一开始就做了一些伸展练习，
that's a good exercise to get your fingers limbered up,
这是让你的手指活动起来的一个很好的练习，
but remember, your hands will stretch over time,
但请记住，你的手会随着时间的推移而伸展，
as you try and do larger and larger forms,
当你尝试做越来越大的形式时，
in the beginning, wow, just to get a barre chord, six string barre chord form,
一开始仅仅是得到第六弦上的横按和弦形式，
we really felt like we had to stretch so much,
我们觉得我们必须伸展这么多，
now we're getting into more complex form,
现在我们进入更复杂的形式，
so we really got to open that hand up.
所以我们要张开那只手。
Okay, here we go,
好了，开始，
let's say play them together,
我们一起说并弹奏，
ready go,
准备，开始，
F, F G A Bb C D E F G A Bb C D E F G A Bb.
F ， F G A Bb C D E F G A Bb C D E F G A Bb 。
Okay, now that is one form of the three note on a string scale,
好的，这是一弦三音的一种形式，
now, how many notes are there in a major scale,
一个大调音阶有多少个音符，
seven, and then we hit the octave, right,
七个，然后我们达到八度，
so there's seven, there's going to be seven different forms patterns of these three note on string scales
所以会有七个不同的一弦三音形式，
as we go up our neck.
随着我们在琴颈的上升。
Okay, so are we just done the first one,
好的，我们刚做完第一个，
okay, now let's do the second one.
好的，现在让我们做第二个。
So now I'm going to do the F scale,
现在我要做 F 音阶，
but I'm going to start on a G,
但是我要从 G 开始，
so I'm starting on the second step of the F scale,
所以我从 F 音阶的第二个开始，
so I shift my hand up here,
所以我把我的手向上移到这里，
first finger is on that third fret G,
食指在三品 G 上，
still same concept, three notes per string,
还是同样的概念，一弦三音，
and I end up with a little bit different finger pattern.
最后我得到一点不同的手指模式。
Let's do this one,
我们来做这个，
G A Bb,
G A Bb ，
C D, big stretch out here to E,
C D 大的伸展到 E ，
F G A,
F G A ，
Bb C D,
Bb C D ，
now I got to stretch
现在我必须伸展，
and shift positions up to fifth position to catch this E,
把位置移到第五把位，才能抓住这个 E ，
I always want the first note of a three to be with my first finger,
我总是希望三个中的第一个音符是在我的食指上，
E F G A Bb C,
E F G A Bb C ，
now you'll notice everything is up one step,
现在你会注意到所有的东西都上升了一级，
not -} only did I start one step up,
我不仅开始升了一级，
but I ended one step up from the other one.
而且结束又升了一级。
Let's do that second form one more time,
让我们再做一次第二个形式，
G, say and play with me,
G ，和我一起说并弹奏，
G A Bb C D E F G A Bb C D E F G A B C.
G A Bb C D E F G A Bb C D E F G A Bb C 。
Okay, that was form two,
好的，这是第二个形式，
I'm gonna quickly go through the other forms as well.
我也会快速看一下其他形式。
We won't spend as much time on them,
我们不会花太多时间在它们上面，
but here's the third form,
但这是第三个形式，
starts on the third part of the scale, the third step of the scale,
从音阶的第三个开始，音阶的第三个，
I put my first finger on this A now,
我把我的食指放在这个 A 上面，
okay, now remember the goal of all this is learning your neck,
好的，记住这一切的目标是学习你的琴颈，
so I would encourage you
所以我鼓励你，
not just to learn the patterns,
不要只是学习模式，
because everybody can learn the patterns,
因为每个人都可以学习模式，
I'm talking about learning the neck,
我说的是学习琴颈，
learn what these notes are,
学习这些音符是什么，
Say them as you're playing them,
边弹边说，
you may not be able to do it the first time through,
你可能不能第一次做到这一点，
but this is the idea of it,
但这就是它的想法，
say the notes,
说出音符，
realize that this is an A, this is an F, this is A Bb,
意识到这是 A ，这是 F ，这是 Bb ，
make that connection between your fingers,
在你的手指之间建立联系，
what you're saying and also thinking about the scale,
你在说什么，也想着音阶，
there's three different things going on.
有三种不同的事情发生。
Here we go,
我们开始，
here the third form,
这是第三种形式，
ready go,
准备，开始，
D E F G A Bb C D E shift F G A Bb C D.
D E F G A Bb C D E F G A Bb C D 。
Next form, starts on the fourth,
下一个形式，从第四个开始，
E F G A B C D E F G A Bb C D E,
E F G A B C D E F G A B C D E ，
okay, we're almost to the top now.
好的，现在我们差不多到达顶端了。
Okay, now let's start on the fifth, on that C,
好的，现在我们从第五个开始，从 C 开始，
C D E F G A Bb C D E F G A Bb C D E F.
C D E F G A Bb C D E F G A Bb C D E F 。
Two more,
另外两个，
starts on the D,
从 D 开始，
D E F G A Bb C D E F G A Bb C D E F.
D E F G A Bb C D E F G A Bb C D E F 。
And the last one starting on this E,
最后一个从这个 E 开始，
E F G A Bb C D E F G A Bb C D E F G A.
E F G A Bb C D E F G A Bb C D E F G A 。
Now we have gone through all the forms now,
现在我们已经看过了所有的形式，
here's what you need to do,
这是你需要做的，
go through all of those forms,
通过所有这些形式，
learn those seven different forms,
学习这七种不同的形式，
and then start doing them in different keys,
然后开始用不同的调做这些，
you'll notice you'll start bouncing around different places on the neck.
你会注意到你开始在琴颈上的不同地方弹跳。
Let me show you a couple of tricks you can do with these
让我给你展示几个你能做的技巧，
and what makes these three on a string scales so helpful, when you play.
以及当你弹奏时，什么让一弦三音如此有帮助。
Here's an exercise you can do,
这里有一个你可以做的练习，
you go up at one and down in the other,
你使用一个往上，另一个往下，
up at one, down in the other,
一个往上，另一个往下，
we did this on pentatonic scales,
我们用五声音阶来做，
let's see how it works out with three note on a string scales.
让我们来看看一弦三音音阶是如何工作的。
Starting down here in first position again,
再次从这里第一把位开始，
it'll be something like this,
它大概是这样的，
now I switch and shift positions
现在我交换移动位置，
and I go down in the second form
然后我在第二种形式，
and I go up
我再向上，
and so on.
等等。
Now you can also do hammer-ons and pull-offs, when you're doing this,
当你做这个的时候，你也可以做击弦和勾弦，
okay, so you do hammer-ons ascending
好的，所以你做击弦向上，
and of course pull-offs as you're descending,
做勾弦向下，
hammer-ons, so I just,
击弦，所以我只是，
if I did that on this first form,
如果我在第一个形式上这样做，
I just play the first note
我只弹奏第一个音符，
and then hammer on the other two,
然后击弦其他两个音符，
let's shift up and do our pull-offs down,
让我们向上移动，然后做勾弦向下，
takes a little bit of a practice to get control with your hammer-ons and pull-offs,
需要一点练习来控制你的击弦和勾弦，
but here's, here's one of the wonderful guitar tricks you can do with these now.
但这是一个很棒的吉他技巧，你可以用它们来做。
Okay, I'm going to speed that up,
好的，我会加快速度，
okay, and I'm gonna turn my metronome on here
我要打开我的节拍器，
and we're gonna do triplets,
我们要做三连音，
okay, what are triplets,
好的，什么是三连音，
let's talk about that first,
让我们先谈谈这个，
well, eighth notes, there's two per beat,
八分音符，每拍两个，
sixteenth notes, there's four per beat,
十六分音符，每拍四个，
now we're going to talk about the in between one, triplets,
现在我们来谈谈中间的一个，三连音，
with triplets, there are only three per beat,
对于三连音，每拍只有三个，
think of it like this,
这样想，
if here is my beat,
如果这是我的节拍，
eighth notes would be eighth, eighth, eighth, eighth, eighth, eighth, eighth, eighth,
八分音符是八分，八分，八分，八分，八分，八分，八分，八分，
sixteenth would be,
十六分音符是，
triplets would be,
三分音符是，
one, two, three, one two three, one two three, one two three,
1 2 3 ， 1 2 3 ， 1 2 3 ， 1 2 3 ，
saturday, saturday, saturday, saturday,
星期六，星期六，星期六，星期六，
sometimes you help putting things to syllables helps out like that,
有时你把东西拼成音节会有这样的帮助，
that's what triplets are.
这就是三连音。
So if I have a measure of eighth notes,
所以，如果我有一个八分音符小节，
followed by a measure of triplets,
后面跟着一个三连音的小节，
it would be eighth, eighth, eighth, eighth, eighth, eighth, eighth, eighth,
那就是八分，八分，八分，八分，八分，八分，八分，八分，
triplet, triplet, triplet, triplet,
三分，三分，三分，三分，
see how triplets work.
看到三连音是如何工作的。
Now let's put some triplets with our three note on a string scales.
现在让我们把三连音放在一弦三音上。
Okay, this is pretty slow, this is 60 beats per minute,
好的，这是相当慢的，这是每分钟 60 次，
and I do my hammer-ons and I'm gonna do triplets,
我要做击弦和三连音，
so it be something like this,
所以，它是像这样的东西，
go,
开始，
good, let's crank it up a little bit,
好的，让我们把它调高一点，
maybe up to 72 here,
也许升高到 72 ，
I do the same thing again, go,
我做同样的事，开始，
now, what works out great with these is
现在这些东西最好的地方是，
I'm not actually having to pick,
我不需要拨动，
which picking is the hardest part of building speed,
拨动是构建速度最难的部分，
not necessarily the fingering,
而不一定是指法，
it's your picking hand,
这是你的拨动的手，
that's the one thing that starts screwing up after a while.
这是一件一段时间之后开始搞砸的事情。
So let's raise it up a little bit,
所以让我们把它调高一点，
let's put up in 100 here,
我们调高到 100 ，
so the triplets are like,
所以三连音就像，
okay, and then you would go on, so on.
好的，然后你就可以继续了。
Crank it up a little bit more,
把它调得更快一点，
let's do like maybe 120,
我们使用 120 ，
okay, I'm going pretty fast at that point,
好的，我在这次弹得很快，
I still have room to go,
我还有地方要走，
because I haven't maxed out my picking hand yet.
因为我的拨动的手还没到极限。
So let's go up a little bit more, 144,
所以让我们再往上一点， 144 ，
suddenly, I've got a really cool way,
突然间，我有了一种非常酷的方式，
I can play through scales
我可以弹奏音阶，
and get a lot of good distance on the neck,
并在琴颈上得到很多好的距离，
all I need to do is kick in, maybe a little distortion,
我所需要做的就是开始加入一些失真，
let's throw a little delay on that,
让我们加一点延迟，
get this going one more time
这个再来一次，
and turn that off a little bit.
把它调低一点。
Okay, all [] flipping off those three note on the string scales,
好的，这都[]一弦三音音阶，
it all starts with learning your seven positions of it,
开始于学习它的七种把位，
yeah, seven positions, it's a lot,
是的，七种把位，这很多，
took me about three months to get it all,
我花了大约三个月的时间才全部掌握，
but every day I would go through these in all the different keys
但我每天都会用所有不同的调来弹奏这些，
and it would take [] the start,
这在开始花费[]，
but eventually you get to sing those patterns more and more,
但最终你会越来越多地唱这些模式，
say and play the notes all the way up the neck
说和弹奏整个琴颈上的音符，
and you'll learn the neck of your instrument
你会学习琴颈上的东西，
and get a really cool thing that you can do,
得到一件你可以做的非常酷的事情，
and you can solo with using hammer-on and pull-offs for these three string scales.
你可以 solo ，使用击弦和勾弦在这些一弦三音音阶。
Okay, welcome to the how music works section,
好的，欢迎来到音乐工作原理部分，
here we're gonna learn a real helpful little bit complex of topic,
我们将学习一个非常有帮助的复杂的话题，
but we're into, I mean we're at what, session 17,
我们进入了，我是说，我们在第 17 节课，
we're into complex stuff now,
我们现在进入了复杂的话题，
this is one of the most helpful things is seventh chords,
这是最有帮助的事情之一，是七和弦，
we've talked about triads, majors, minors, diminished, augmented,
我们已经讨论了三和弦，大调，小调，弱化，增强，
now I'm going to just going to add one more third on top of that triad,
现在我要在三和弦的基础上再加一个三音，
and we're gonna make a seventh chord out of it.
我们要用它来产生七和弦。
Okay, now you've already been playing seventh chords, C7, D7, G7,
好的，你已经弹奏了七和弦 C7 D7 G7 ，
now, we're gonna talk about the different kinds of seventh chords
现在我们将讨论七和弦的不同种类，
and what exactly they are in music.
以及它们在音乐中的确切含义。
When I say a seventh chord, that involves four tones,
当我说第七和弦时，它涉及四个音调，
the first, the third, the fifth and the seventh degree of the major scale.
大调音阶的第一、三、五、七度。
Now that I've got more notes,
现在我有了更多的音符，
I've got more different permutations,
我有了更多的不同的排列，
that I can have with those different notes,
我可以用这些不同的音符，
so, I end up with a bunch of different combinations,
所以我最终得到了一堆不同的组合，
so let's go through those really quickly.
所以让我们快速地看一遍。
The first one, one, three, five and seven is called a major seventh chord,
第一个和弦，一，三，五和七被称为大七和弦，
whether it's in C F Bb, whatever,
无论是在 C F Bb 什么都行，
if it's a major seventh chord,
如果它是一个大七和弦，
that major, very important major seventh chord,
大调，非常重要的大七和弦，
then you're dealing with the first, third, fifth and seventh degree of that C scale
那么你处理的是 C 音阶的第一，三，五和七度，
or whatever scale you're in,
或者你在的任何音阶，
if I am in C,
如果我在 C 音阶，
it'd be a C E G and a B,
它会是 C E G 和 B ，
that would be the notes in A C major seven.
那就是 C 大七和弦的音符。
Okay, the next one is a minor seventh,
好的，下一个是小七和弦，
well, what is that minor telling us,
那个小调告诉我们什么，
that's telling us triad information,
它告诉我们三和弦信息，
so instead of one, three, five,
所以不是 1 3 5 ，
it's now one, b3, five,
现在是 1 b3 5 ，
now, let's talk about the seventh,
现在，让我们来谈谈第七个，
it's a b7,
这是一个 b7 ，
why is it a b7.
为什么是 b7 。
Well, here is the rule,
好的，规则是这样的，
always use a b7, except for two exceptions,
总是使用 b7 ，除了两个例外，
Okay, the first of which we're going to talk about,
好的，第一个我们要谈到，
and the second, which I'll talk about in a minute.
第二个，我会马上谈到。
The first exception is our major seventh,
第一个例外是我们的大七和弦，
when I say the word major seventh,
当我说 major seventh 时，
I've got to physically say the word major seventh
我必须说大调七，
or in your chord it'll have an maj7
或者在你的和弦中有一个 maj7 ，
or even sometimes you'll see a triangle,
甚至有时你会看到一个三角形，
that's the abbreviation, [] Jazz abbreviation for major seventh.
它是[]爵士大七和弦的缩写。
Okay, it has to physically say major seventh,
好的，它必须是大七和弦，
otherwise, if it doesn't say that,
否则，如果它不这么说，
it's a flat seventh, always,
它就是降七，总是这样，
except for one other exception, I'll tell you about in a second,
除了另一个例外，我马上会告诉你，
but all the time it's a flat seventh,
但它一直都是降七，
unless it says major seventh,
除非它写的是大七，
okay, so C minor seventh would then be C Eb G,
好的，所以 C 小调七就是 C Eb G ，
and then the flat at seventh would be a Bb,
然后在降七是 Bb ，
if I played it,
如果我弹奏它，
it would be C Eb G Bb.
它将是 C Eb G Bb 。
Okay, next one is a dominant 7th,
好的，下一个是属七和弦，
now you don't hear, hear it referred to as a dominant seventh very much,
现在没有听到属七和弦很多次，
that's kind of the technical name of it,
这是一种技术上的名称，
when you just say I want to C seventh and F seventh,
当你说我想要 C7 或 F7 ，
not a minor seventh, not a major seventh, just seventh,
不是小七和弦，不是大七和弦，只是七和弦，
when it's just a seventh, it's a dominant seventh.
当它只是七时，它就是属七和弦。
The formula for that is one, three, five, flated seventh,
它的模式是 1 3 5 b7 ，
so if I'm in C, it would be C E G Bb.
所以如果我在 C 中，它将是 C E G Bb 。
Now, okay,
现在，好的，
next one is augmented seventh,
下一个增七和弦，
that would be an augmented triad, C E G#,
这是一个增强的三和弦， C E G# ，
sharp the fifth, right, one, three, sharp five
增强 5 ， 1 3 #5 ，
and still what kind of seventh, flatted seventh,
仍然是，什么样的七， b7 ，
C E G# Bb.
C E G# Bb 。
Okay, now here comes our two,
好的，现在是我们的两个，
this last one, the diminished chord, has two little branches of it,
最后一个，减弱和弦，有两个小分支，
let's talk about the first one,
我们来谈谈第一个，
if I want a fully diminished seventh chord,
如果我想要一个完全减七和弦，
diminished tells us one, flat three, flat five, just like the triad,
减弱告诉我们， 1 b3 b5 ，就像三和弦一样，
now, what happens with the seventh,
那么第七会发生什么，
Well, here's our second exception from our rule,
好的，这是我们规则中的第二个例外，
it is a double flatted seventh,
这是一个双降的第七，
when you're in a fully diminished chord,
当你在完全的减弱和弦时，
it is a double flated seventh,
它就是双降的第七和弦，
why is that,
为什么会这样，
I don't know, that's just how it is.
我不知道，它就是这样。
The formula for a fully diminished chord is
完全减弱和弦的模式是，
C, excuse me, one, flat three, flat five, double flat seven,
C ，抱歉， 1 b3 b5 bb7 ，
C Eb Gb Bbb,
C Eb Gb Bbb ，
but Steve, isn't that an A,
但是， Steve ，这难道不是 A 吗，
yes, I know that's an A, you know that's an A,
是的，我知道这是一个 A ，你知道这是一个 A ，
but in theory land which is where we're right now,
但是理论上，我们现在就在那里，
it is a Bbb,
它是一个 Bbb ，
okay.
好的。
Now, there's also his sister is a half diminished,
现在，还有他的姐妹是半减弱，
the formula for a half diminished is one, flat three, flat five, flat seven,
半减七和弦的公式是 1 b3 b5 b7 ，
I know there's a lot of formulas I'm throwing at you,
我知道我向你抛出了很多公式，
that's the last of them, okay,
这是最后一批了，好吗，
so what is that,
所以这是什么，
we've got, what, six different forms there,
我们有六种不同的形式，
half diminished, one, flat three, flat five, double flat, or excuse me, regular flat seven,
半减， 1 b3 b5 双降，抱歉，常规的 b7 ，
so in C, it be C Eb Gb Bb.
所以在 C 中，它是 C Eb Gb Bb 。
Okay, here's the rule,
好的，规则是这样的，
everything's always a flat seventh
所有的东西都是降七的，
except for when it says physically says major seventh
除非它的物理上说是大七，
or it's a fully diminished seventh and then it would be a double flat.
或者它是完全减弱的七，然后它就会是双降。
Okay, so let's do a little bit of practice,
好的，让我们来做一点练习，
what would be a Cmaj7,
Cmaj7 是什么，
well, the formula would be one, three, five, seven,
好的，公式是 1 3 5 7 ，
so in C, it would be a C E G B,
所以在 C 中，它是 C E G B ，
what would be a Cm7,
Cm7 是什么，
what's the formula, one, flat three, five, flat seven,
方程是什么， 1 b3 5 b7 ，
C Eb G Bb,
C Eb G Bb ，
what about a C7,
C7 是什么，
no problem, one, three, five, flat seven, C E G Bb.
没问题， 1 3 5 b7 ， C E G Bb 。
Okay, well Steve,
好的， Steve ，
what, what on earth good could there be from all of this math in the seventh chords,
从第七和弦的所有这些数学中到底有什么好处，
well, as I'm reading through a chord progression
好的，当我读和弦进程的时候，
and here's an, let's say an Em7 stare me in the face
这里有一个假设是 Em7 在我前面，
and I want to solo over the top of that,
我想要在上面 solo ，
I need to know what notes are in that Em7,
我想知道 Em7 有什么音符，
I can't just fake it,
我不能假装它，
that's what I did when I was, that's the baby pool,
我[小时候]就是这么干的，
when you just kind of fake it
当你假装它的时候，
and you you play something in the key,
你在调中弹了一些东西，
now I want to know exactly what those notes are,
现在我想知道这些音符到底是什么，
in an Em7, that's one, flat three, five, flat seven, E G B and D,
在 Em7 中，那是 1 b3 5 b7 ， E G B D ，
here comes that chord,
这就是和弦，
it's time for me to solo,
是我 solo 的时候了，
the guy points to me, I'm ready to solo,
那家伙指着我，我准备好 solo 了，
the four tones I know are super safe,
我知道的这四个音是很安全的，
are E G B and D,
就是 E G B D ，
because I know the chord tones.
因为我知道和弦音。
So yes, those chords are coming by,
所以，是的，这些和弦正在到来，
but you start thinking of those chords as combinations of tones,
但你开始认为这些和弦是音调的组合，
which tones are common throughout all those different chords,
哪些音调在所有不同的和弦中是共同的，
and you start being able to understand how to build a good solo.
你开始能够理解如何建立一个好的 solo 。
Soloing is coming up in one of the later sessions,
solo 将在后面的课程中出现，
but this is the beginning of it
但这只是它的开始，
and you have to have this harmonic understanding underneath your belt,
你必须在有一个[和谐]的理解，
so where when you see an Fm7,
当你看到 Fm7 时，
you know what that is and what formula goes with it.
你知道那是什么，以及与之相配的公式。
Okay.
好的。
Here's our assignment for this session.
这是我们这节课的作业。
I want you to practice your three note on a string scales,
我想要你练习一弦三音，
the full range of the instrument,
乐器的所有范围，
in various keys,
在不同的调上，
try and do them in all the keys,
试着在所有的调上做，
if you're interested in learning,
如果你对学习很感兴趣，
and if you're this deep into this series,
如果你对这一系列有如此深入的了解，
you're pretty serious about learning,
你对学习是相当认真的，
so I encourage you to do them in all the keys,
所以我鼓励你在所有的调上都这样做，
say and play the notes,
说并弹奏音符，
learn the neck,
学习琴颈，
there's no easy way to do it,
没有简单的方法，
you got to say them and play them
你必须说出它们，弹奏它们，
and understand what these notes are,
并理解这些音符是什么，
I wish I could give you a magic formula for doing it,
我希望能给你一个神奇的公式来做到这个，
but a lot of it is sitting on your couch and doing this for a lot of times
但其中很多都是坐在你的沙发上，反复做很多次，
until you can get those where you understand where these notes are,
直到你明白这些音符在哪里，
so the key to opening that door of knowledge,
所以打开知识之门的钥匙，
I found is through these three note on string scales,
我发现是通过一弦三音，
say and play all keys, the full range of the instrument.
说并弹奏所有调，乐器的全部范围。
Now then you get into the guitar playing fun stuff,
现在，你开始弹吉他有趣的东西，
do the hammer, practice the hammer-ons and the pull-offs with them,
练习击弦和勾弦，
eventually, you'll be able to get him going pretty fast,
最终你会让他跑得很快，
try not going from beginning to end,
试着不要从头到尾，
try somewhere starting somewhere in the middle,
试着从中间的某个地方开始，
going up a little bit, coming down a little bit,
往上一点，往下一点，
get that control over those hammer-ons and pull-offs,
控制住那些击弦和勾弦，
slow, steady is where you want them,
缓慢而稳定就是你想要的，
incorporate triplets into that as well.
也跟三连音一起弹奏。
There's plenty of exercise in your book for you to start on,
你的书里有很多练习可供你开始练习，
and Jam Along exercises for you to get some practice in the soloing, which is coming up.
Jam Along 练习让你练习一些 solo ，它即将到来。
Okay, I'll see you at the workshop.
好的，我们在 workshop 见。
In our workshop time,
在我们的 workshop 时间里，
I want to cover several key things,
我想谈几件关键的事情，
three note on a string scales.
一弦三音。
Let's go through that first form very slowly,
让我们非常慢地看一下第一种形式，
let me turn on my metronome here,
让我在这里打开我的节拍器，
we're going to start an F, down here at the first form,
我们将从 F 开始，向下这里的第一个形式，
try and say and play the notes
试着说并弹奏这些音符，
as we do them together,
我们一起做，
ready, go,
准备，开始，
F G A Bb C D E F G A Bb C D E F G A Bb C,
F G A Bb C D E F G A Bb C D E F G A Bb C ，
that was a little fast,
这有点快了，
let me slow that down a little bit,
让我放慢一点速度，
give you a chance to catch up,
给你一个赶上的机会，
now, a little bit slower, ready, play,
现在，慢一点了，准备，开始，
F G A Bb C D, stretch out that hand,
F G A Bb C D ，拉伸那只手，
E F G A Bb C D E F G A Bb,
E F G A Bb C D E F G A Bb ，
okay.
好的。
Now let's transpose that to a different key,
现在让我们把它换成不同的调，
let's say I'm doing it in the key of G,
假设我的调是 G ，
I'm going to move everything up a whole step,
我要把所有的音调都往上移一步，
now I'm going to do that same form in the key of G,
现在我要用 G 调做同样的形式，
I want you to say the notes,
我想要你把音符说出来，
ready, play,
准备，弹奏，
G A B C D E F# G A B C D E F# G A B C,
G A B C D E F# G A B C D E F# G A B C ，
let's do it one more,
让我们再来一个，
let's do it in the key of C,
让我们用 C 调来做，
no problem,
没问题，
move my first finger up here to C,
将我的第一个手指向上移动到 C ，
ready go,
准备，开始，
C D E F G A B C D E F G A B C D E F G,
C D E F G A B C D E F G A B C D E F G ，
now let's speed up a little bit,
现在让我们快一点，
okay,
好的，
let's go back to, let's do it in Bb,
让我们回到，让我们来做 Bb ，
okay, ready go,
好的，准备，开始，
Bb C D,
Bb C D ，
speed it up a little bit more
再快一点，
and I'm going to start an F,
我从 F 开始，
actually, let me put it down, we'll do it in triplets,
事实上，让我把它降下来，我们将做三连音，
okay, start F, we're gonna go ascending one way,
好的，从 F 开始，我们从一个往上，
shift up and descending the next
往上移，从下一个往下，
and I'm gonna work my way all the way up the neck in triplets,
我要用三连音弹完整个琴颈，
ready, go,
准备，开始，
now I went the entire full length of the instrument,
现在，我把乐器的整个长度都拿了出来，
from the lowest note, I was able to hit in that key
从我能碰到的那个调最低的音符开始，
to the highest note I was able to hit in that key,
到我能碰到的那个调的最高音符，
that's what I would like for you to do
这就是我希望你所做的，
in all these other forms and in the other keys as well.
在所有这些其他形式和其他调中。
Let's do it one more time,
让我们再来一次，
let me speed it up a little bit,
让我把速度加快一点，
now I'm gonna do it, let's say in C,
现在我要做，假设是 C ，
but I'm gonna start down here,
但我要从这里开始，
so I gotta start in a different form, okay,
所以我要从另一种形式开始，好吗，
but I'm gonna be in the key of C,
但我会是 C 调，
let's do hammer-ons,
让我们做击弦，
ready, go,
准备，开始，
that's as high as I can get,
这是我能得到的最高的，
Okay.
好的。
Do those on all the keys
做这些在所有调中，
try and say and play the notes as you're doing them,
在你做的时候，试着说并弹奏音符，
that's where you start learning.
这就是你开始学习的地方。
Let's spell a couple of seventh chords before we go,
在我们结束之前，让我们拼写几个七和弦，
okay, what would be Dm7,
好的，什么是 Dm7 ，
what the formula, one, flat three, five, flat seven,
公式是什么， 1 b3 5 b7 ，
plug those numbers into a D scale,
把这些数字加入 D 音阶，
you end up with D F A and C,
你就会得到 D F A C ，
what would an Amaj7 be,
Amaj7 是什么，
A C# E G#,
A C# E G# ，
what would Bb7 be,
Bb7 是什么，
Bb D F Ab.
Bb D F Ab 。
As you're looking at music,
当你在看音乐的时候，
try and always be spelling these seventh chords as they come by,
试着拼写这些七和弦，
now that you know what notes are involved in them,
因为你知道它们涉及到什么音符，
this is a long process of learning these scales,
这是一个学习这些音阶的漫长过程，
but it's very, very helpful,
但它非常非常有帮助，
play and say the notes,
弹奏和说这些音符，
give yourself some time to do this,
给自己一些时间来做这件事，
this is gonna take some weeks to get this underneath your your belt,
这可能需要几个星期的时间才能让你明白，
but perseverance will pay off in what you're doing,
但坚持不懈会在你所做的事情中得到回报，
I'll see you next time.
我们下次再见。